[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the definition of the term hypercarnivore?", "correct_answer": "An animal whose diet consists exclusively of meat.", "incorrect_answers": ["It is a synonym for apex carnivore.", "A predator that feeds on carnivorous animals.", "It is a term that refers to humans."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Portal circulation refers to the circulation of blood returning from the body and entering the heart through semilunar portals.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "One of the people who voiced Bambi became a career Marine, served in two theaters of war, but never killed an animal.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which character is frozen in carbonite near the end of Episode V?", "correct_answer": "Han Solo", "incorrect_answers": ["Leia Organa", "Chewbacca", "Luke Skywalker"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What body part is involved in the medical procedure called orchiopexy?", "correct_answer": "Testicle", "incorrect_answers": ["Teeth", "Tendons", "Navel"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Independence State is one of the nicknames of this U.S. state.", "correct_answer": "Pennsylvania", "incorrect_answers": ["Virginia", "New Hampshire", "West Virginia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the revolutionary tornado research device made by Bill Paxton and Helen Hunts characters in the disaster flick Twister?", "correct_answer": "Dorothy", "incorrect_answers": ["D.O.T.", "Twister", "T.O.T.O"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what year was Jurassic Park released on the big screen?", "correct_answer": "1993", "incorrect_answers": ["1994", "1997", "1995"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "According to the film The Lost Boys, Santa Carla is also known by what other name?", "correct_answer": "the murder capital of the world", "incorrect_answers": ["the vampire capital of the world", "The town didnt have another name in the film.", "the carnival capital of the world"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Dianthus caryophyllus, or carnation,  was originally grown in which colour?", "correct_answer": "Pink", "incorrect_answers": ["Green", "Yellow", "White"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What famous Israeli liqueur comes in a genie shaped bottle and has a distinctive chocolate/orange flavor?", "correct_answer": "Sabra", "incorrect_answers": ["Triple Sec", "Cointreau", "Grand Marnier"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the sci-fi movie Aliens, what was the name of the ship that brought Ripley and company back to LV-426?", "correct_answer": "Sulaco", "incorrect_answers": ["Goodhope", "Pegasus", "Argo"]}]